hi my frends
green silence
camping at altitude
Fallen trees in the valley are alive, that's why I tie the sticks to the tree with thread
I put a piece of wood underneath for more resistance
In the previous video, I have included the method of making and tying the ladder
Refer to the description
When the rain hits the tree trunk, it becomes very slippery, that's why I installed the rope
Sugar
flour
baking powder
I leave it in a warm place to rest
The dough increased
But it's not a problem, I'm very hungry
♨️
black tea
I was very lucky because if the camera was thrown from a height of three meters, there would be no video
Thanks for watching